奥列格 第二桌的客人
Oleg, the people at table two
想知道他们的蔬菜汉堡里有什么
want to know what's in the veggie burger.
不 他们不会想知道的
No. They don't.
好吧 无所谓
Eh. That's fine.
他们还想要再添
They wanted refills,
所以我估计也不会再过去了
so I'm probably not gonna go back there anyway.
麦克斯上哪去了
Where's Max?
这菜在这边放了这么久
This plate has been here so long,
里面的三文鱼都要变成沙门氏菌[音似]了
the salmon is turning into Salmonella.
她跟新来的洗碗工去"休息"一下了
She took a break with the new dishwasher.
麦克斯 我还以为你从后面溜出去了
Max, I thought you slipped out the back.
他的确"溜出来"了一会 但我又帮他塞回去了
He did for a minute, but I popped him back in.
新闻快讯 跟你的同事上床
This just in, work is so much more fun
会让工作变得欢乐无边
when you're sleeping with a co-worker.
麦克斯 刚才的确很爽
Max, that was good.
喊五次额滴神啊的爽度
It was five Hail Marys good.
我们让这些脏盘子变更"脏"了
I think we made these dishes dirtier.
麦克斯 他的确很萌
Max, he's cute,
但听到他这口音你怎么还硬得起来
but how can you even stay hard with that accent?
"狗来 麦克苏 让偶跟里爱爱一下下"
"Come here, Max. I wanna hump ya a wee bit".
我能说啥 我一直对
What can I say, I always had a thing
幸运符麦片盒上的小人情有独钟(爱尔兰妖精)
for the guy on the box of Lucky Charms.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
看 我买了个健美计步器
Look, I got me a Fitbit.
只要再走二十万步
Only 200,000 more steps
婚礼上就能身材"健美" "步步"生莲了
before I get a bit more fit for my wedding.
很厉害了
That's impressive.
我连十二步都走不完呢
I couldn't even make it through 12 steps.
麦克斯
Hey, Max.
我的伴娘你还好吗
How's my maid of honor?
卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
我平凡无奇的婚礼宾客你还好吗
How's my run-of-the-mill wedding guest?
我很好 这话说得有说服力吗
I'm doing great. Did that sound convincing?
我每天早上都花一小时在浴室里
'Cause I've been practicing it in the bathroom mirror
对着镜子练习回答这问题
for an hour every morning.
我看过 以后你在练习时
I know, I've got to stop sitting on the toilet
我就不进去蹲坑了
while you do that.
麦克斯 来谈谈伴娘礼服
Max, let's talk bridesmaid dresses.
我无所谓 你给我啥我都穿
I don't care, I'll wear anything.
我穿灰狗大巴司机制服去参加高中舞会呢
I wore a Greyhound Bus driver's uniform to my prom.
我当时刚下班就直接去了
I was coming straight from work.
我已经决定要穿
Well, I have decided to wear
科臣斯基奶奶当年的婚纱
Grandma Kuchenski's wedding gown.
对啊 我家族里所有的女人都穿
Yeah, all of the women in my family wore it.
除了我丝薇提与蕾提阿姨
Everyone except aunts Svetti and Letti,
那是因为她们是腹部连着的连体婴
'cause, well, they're attached at the abdomen.
她来了
There she is.
我墨西哥大香肠蛋饼必备的火辣辣酱
The hot sauce for my Huevos Mancheros.
苏菲宝贝 我弄到你想要的那个了
Hey, Sophie, baby, I got you what you want.
奥列格 没人想要肝炎好吗
Oleg, no one wants hepatitis.
正式定下了
It's official.
我们的婚礼会出现在《时报》上
Our wedding's gonna be in The Times.
奥列格 你凭什么能上《时报》
Oleg, how are you gonna be in The Times?
人家《时报》很挑剔的哇
The Times tends to be picky
而你是属于"很挑剔的挖"鼻屎
and you tend to be more "picky your nose."
我的第二次婚礼就上《时报》呢
You know, my second wedding made The Times.
因为我的第一任妻子跑来往我脚开了一枪
'Cause my first wife showed up and shot me in the leg.
是薇兰卡 我妹
That's Vlanka, my sister.
她是我另一个伴娘
She's my other bridesmaid.
其实我跟她不太亲 不过我可怜她
Yeah, we're not that close, but I feel bad for her
因为她是那种都成年了还长雀斑的人
'cause she's one of those adults with freckles.
麦克斯 你会上《时报》呢
Max, you're going to be in The Times!
上《时报》 然后穿着苏菲挑的鬼东西
In The Times, wearing God knows what Sophie will pick.
她可是有一抽屉"健身时戴的王冠"的那种人
I mean, she has a drawer full of diamond tiaras for the gym.
您好 请问姐两位在聊啥呢
Hello, what are you two talking about?
在讨论要故意忽视哪桌客人吗
Deciding which tables to ignore?
我们在讨论苏菲的品味
We're talking about Sophie's taste.
我去 小婊砸们
Oh, bitch, please.
别闹了
Come on.
我早餐纤维棒都比她的品味来得"好味"
My morning fiber cookie has better taste than Sophie.
姑娘们 薇兰卡滚蛋了
Girls, Vlanka's out.
雀斑妹就算了 还有胆跟老娘叫板
She has an attitude and freckles.
对啊 这也太超过了
Yeah. I mean, that's too far.
所以 恭喜你啦 卡洛琳
So, Caroline, congratulations!
你就是我新的伴娘啦
You're my new bridesmaid!
我找到我喜欢的伴娘礼服了
Okay, I found a bridesmaid's dress that I like.
但我们买得起的唯一办法是
But the only way we can afford it is
把你卖给分类广告网上那个亚美尼亚人
if I sell you to that Armenian guy on Craigslist.
屁咧
No way.
他们爱吃的鹰嘴豆泥 我吃几口就想吐
I get sick of hummus after four bites.
麦克斯 这件事我们得占据主导权
Max, we have to take charge of this.
因为无论苏菲给我们挑了什么婚纱
Because whatever bridesmaid's dress Sophie picks
都会像泰勒·派瑞导的电影一样
is like a Tyler Perry movie.
我看都不用看就知道难看到死
I don't have to see it to know it's gonna be awful.
我们就自己找件高雅漂亮的
We'll find something classy, and beautiful,
然后强行逼她接受[硬塞进她喉咙]
and just shove it down her throat.
谁要把什么东西塞进谁的喉咙啊
Who's shoving what down whom?
如果这个你们没有故事说 我有
And if you don't have a story, I do.
强哥 我和麦克斯被人情绑架去当伴娘
John, Max and I got roped into being bridesmaids.
别说了
Stop.
你刚才的"绑"字让我两眼放光
You had me at rope.
但"伴娘"两个字让我兴趣全无
You lost me at bridesmaids.
我会在迎宾员那里站着 看看礼服
I'll be at the hostess stand, looking at dresses
然后默默地祈祷有颗小行星
and silently wishing for an asteroid
撞上地球 灭了全世界
to wipe us off the planet.
如果祈祷这玩意有效 那现在地球上
If wishes made things happen, we'd been in the middle
应该早就被行尸给毁灭世界了
of a zombie apocalypse right now.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
我刚收到从波兰寄来的婚纱了
My dress just arrived from Poland
我等不及要给你们俩看了
and I'm bustin' for you to see it.
一边看 一边吃着你们14块钱一个的布丁
See it while I eat one of your $14 puddings.
苏菲 我有在研究礼服颜色
Sophie, I've been looking at color choices,
你觉得我们两个穿肉色[裸身]如何
and how would you feel about us in a nude?
麦克斯有本钱能裸身
Max could go nude but
但你胸口余额不足 裸身就算了吧
you don't have the rack to pull it off.
有人有刀吗
Does anyone have a knife?
麦克斯 为什么你在甜品吧工作
Max, why do you have a switchblade
身上却会带着弹簧刀啊
to work in a dessert bar?
我妈从小叮咛我出门要带"保护措施"
My mother always told me to carry protection.
屏息以待科臣斯基奶奶的婚纱吧
Wait 'til you see Grandma Kuchenski's dress.
因为强逼吉普赛人当劳工是非法的了
You know, forced gypsy labor is illegal now.
来看看
Here we go.
苏菲 你奶奶是千年老妖吗
Sophie, was your grandma the Crypt Keeper?
外面这是怎么回事
What's going on out here?
空气中这些白色粉末是啥玩意
What's all that white powder in the air?
我是想开餐厅 不是80年代吸白粉的舞厅
I'm trying to run a restaurant, not an 80's disco.
闭上你的鸟嘴
Oh, put a sock in it.
我可是买了你抢钱布丁的贵客
I'm buying one of your freaking overpriced puddings.
我本来要发火的 可现在又有点被你吸引
I'd get mad but I'm mildly attracted to you right now.
只是有点而已吗
Just mildly?
现在我倒是要发火了
I mean, now I'm getting mad.
抱歉 婚礼的烦心事
Sorry. Wedding drama.
她的婚纱突然就灰飞烟灭了
Her dress just fell completely to pieces...
就像我预测中自己不久后的将来
like I'm assuming I'll do in the near future.
婚礼需要任何东西
Whatever you need bridal,
就去布鲁克林区的罗森福家买
go to Rosenfeld's in Brooklyn.
在我又穷又直的那会 我去那里买的婚纱
That's where I got my dress when I was broke and straight.
原来你不是一直都是拉拉啊
So you weren't always into women?
我一直都是拉拉啊
Of course I was.
除了加入邪教的那三年
Except those three years in Scientology.
看来我们三个
Well, it looks like the three of us
得去逛一下婚纱和礼服了
are going to go dress shopping now.
是啊 不过我得先去洗一下手
Yeah. And you know, I got to go wash my hands
我现在手上沾满了老女人的DNA
'cause they're covered in old lady DNA.
看来是得去一趟了
Well, that's that.
跟苏菲去逛街就跟当年
Shopping with Sophie is like when I worked
我在泰式按摩院工作时一样
in a Thai massage parlor.
都得"下去"
We are going down.
但如果我们早苏菲一步去
Not if we go before Sophie
把她会喜欢的难看伴娘裙全藏起来就没事了
and hide every ugly bridesmaid's dress that Sophie would like.
如果她看不到 就不能逼我们穿啦
If she can't see them, she can't make us wear them.
你怎么这么快就能想出这招
How did you come up with that so fast?
我在2010年时就用过这招了
It's the same plan I used in 2010
那年我给克林顿总统女儿当伴娘
when I was a bridesmaid for Chelsea Clinton.
伴娘服难看 她的色鬼老爸还跟踪我进衣帽间
Bad dress and then her father followed me into the coat room.
看看这地方
Look at this place.
让我想起那部电影
It reminds me of that movie.
-《伴娘》吗 -不 是《猛鬼街》
- Bridesmaids? - No, Nightmare on Elm Street.
卡洛琳 我不知道你有什么好担心的
I don't know what you're worried about, Caroline.
我觉得它们都挺漂漂啊
I think they're all quite lovely.
纳西 别说了
Nash, please.
你就是个从爱尔兰来的穷人
You're a poor person from Ireland.
如果我是想知道哪里免费腿部支架之类的
I'll ask your opinion when I need to know where to go
我会问你
to get free leg braces.
麦克斯 你还真没说错
You were right, Max.
她有时候真的就是个"B"
She can be a real "B" sometimes.
对不起啦 但我真不知道为什么带他来
I'm sorry, but I don't even know why he's here.
上你·没商量先生来这
Bonin' O'Brien here...
用美色帮我们引开那些女销售员
is gonna distract the sales lady
然后我们就能藏起那些难看礼服
while we hide the ugly dresses.
您好 女士们
Hello, ladies.
计划不变
Same plan.
谁是那位幸运的新娘啊
Who's the lucky bride?
或者我该问 哪位老阴有幸吃到这小鸡啊
Or should I say, who's the lucky cradle robber?
别理我
Don't mind me.
我这人的幽默感有点疯狂
It's just my crazy sense of humor.
这里的女顾客们都很喜欢
Oh, the ladies here love it.
她们都叫我"疯狂卡尔"
The call me "Crazy Carl."
"你们有听到疯狂卡尔刚才说了什么吗"
"Did you hear what Crazy Carl said?"
她们爱死了
They just love it.
我叫卡洛琳
I'm Caroline.
她叫麦克斯 那男的不是新郎啦
This is Max and he isn't the groom.
不是 绝对不是
No, no, no.
他是单身基 是的
He's single and gay. Yes.
基到都被也很基的"单向组合"给踢出去了
So gay, he got kicked out of One Direction.
你们两个怎么不去一边聊聊
Why don't you two walk off somewhere
分享一下当年出柜所碰到的辛酸呢
and share poignant coming-out stories.
去吧
Go.
-可是 麦克斯... -你听到娘娘下旨了 快去
- But Max-- - Oh, you heard the women, go.
没问题
Can do.
姑娘们 慢慢逛 我们大概...
Ladies, look around, we'll be back...
一个月后就回来
in about a month.
有人要去塔希提共渡蜜月吗
Tahiti anyone?
我是疯狂卡尔嘛
I'm just Crazy Carl.
姑娘们爱死我说笑了
The ladies love it.
伴娘礼服应该改个更贴切的名字
Bridesmaid's dresses should be called what they are.
"像送一大笔钱给慈善机构"
Really expensive donations to Goodwill.
这件烂吗
Is this one bad?
不啊 这可是名牌的礼服
No. That's a Vera Wang.
但这件就是"冥"牌的礼服了
But this is a very wrong.
藏起来
Hide it.
还有"冥"牌2号也藏起来
Ew. And it's evil twin.
我都不知道化学防护衣还有出羽毛版的
Oh, I didn't know hazmat suits came with feathers.
我的老天啊
Oh my God.
这是我这辈子看过最瞎的东西
This the worst thing I've ever seen.
而我可是见过妓女在路边换棉条的人
And I've seen a prostitute change her tampon on the sidewalk.
你叫谁妓女呢
Who are you calling a prostitute?
这件我们必须得藏起来
This, we've got to hide.
这衣服我扒不下来啊
I can't get this dress off.
你就告诉它 你在谷歌工作
Just tell it you work at Google
你想找个人安定下来就话到衣除了
and you're thinking of settling down.
举起来 举起来 扔到后面里
Lift it up. Lift it up. Dump it back there.
手下留人
Stop!
给我放下奶油糖糖·贝蒂
You put Butterscotch Betty down.
我们只是在找价签啦
Oh, we were just looking for a price tag.
我知道你们这是在干嘛
I know what's going on here.
你们想把好礼服藏起来
You're hiding the good dresses
这样明天半价特卖会
to make sure no one else can get them
就没人跟你们抢了
at our annual half-off sale tomorrow.
是是是 你说对了
Yeah, that's what we're doing.
我们在藏"好"礼服
We're hiding the good dresses.
我才刚抓到一个也想浑水摸鱼的女士
In fact, I just caught another Sneaky Sue.
我叫苏菲
Oh, I'm Sophie.
看看这颜色
Oh, look at the color.
那不是颜色 那是"辐射"
That's not color. That's radiation.
这件礼服独一无二
That dress is a one of a kind.
意思是只有一件吗
Meaning there's only one?
没 我们好衣成双
No, we have two.
而我刚好有两个伴娘
And I have two bridesmaids!
我好爱这种完美的巧合
I love it when life works out perfect like this.
女士们 半价特卖会即将开始
Ladies, our half-off sale will begin in a minute.
瞧瞧这地方
Look at this place.
挤满了饥渴的女人 比肯尼·查斯尼
There are more desperate women crammed in here
演唱会上摇滚区里的饥渴女人还多
than the splash zone at a Kenny Chesney concert.
就是 就像沃尔玛的黑色星期五特卖
I know. It's like Black Friday at Walmart
既然这么像 但愿这里也踩踏事件来踩死我
And like Black Friday, hopefully someone will trample me.
因为多谢这两条奇葩裙 我的人生完了
Cause thanks to these dresses, my life is over.
麦克斯 你有在听吗
Max, did you hear me?
我的人生完了
My life is over.
这话你早在中餐馆忘了给你烤鸭酱时说过了
You said that when the Chinese food place forgot the duck sauce.
抱歉啦 可我早就计划好了另外一个
Well, I'm sorry, but I had a whole other scenario planned
重返《时报》的场景
for my return to The Times.
"企业家凤凰涅槃 浴火重生"
"Entrepreneur rises from the ashes."
而现在我要出现在《时报》上
Now, I'm just going to be in The Times,
不是涅槃 是被捏死的麻雀
looking like a stupid ash.
去啊 姐妹 挤进去
Shoot, girl, just push on through.
我在挤 姐妹 我在挤
I'm pushing, girl. I am pushing.
借过
Excuse us.
继续前进啊 姐妹
Just go, girl.
我可不想那两条黄裙子被人抢走
I don't want anybody else to get those two yellow dresses.
麦克斯 你听见了吗
Max, did you hear that?
有人的品味比苏菲还差
Someone has worst taste than Sophie.
让她们过来
Let them through.
现在我们只需排在她俩后面
Now we just have to hang back here
让她们先进去把裙子抢走
and let them get to those dresses first.
耶 我的人生又美好了
Yay! My life is good again.
麦克斯 卡洛琳 到前面来
Max, Caroline, up here.
美梦一秒钟就破功了吗
What was that, like, a second?
我给你俩在前面留了位子
I saved you a space upfront.
快过来
Come on.
完了
Well, it's over.
只要彩带一被剪开
As soon as they cut that ribbon,
苏菲就会开启美式足球野兽跑锋模式
Sophie's going to Marshawn Lynch everyone who
撞开所有挡着咱俩抢裙子的人
gets in the way of us and those dresses.
只有一个办法能解决
There's only one way out of this.
而且你之前也说了
And you called it earlier.
你必须让人踩
You have to let them trample you.
我是说真的
I'm serious.
我才不要故意让人踩呢
I'm not about to be trampled on purpose.
如果你不愿意
See if you still feel that way
看这句话能否改变你的主意
after I say these next few words:
"照片左边那位是 卡洛琳·钱宁"
"Pictured from left, Caroline Channing."
麻烦帮我挡开任何踩向我眼睛的高跟鞋
Try to fend off any heels you see heading for my eyes.
注意啦 女士们
Attention, ladies.
正如你们所见 我手里拿着大剪刀
As you see, I have the big scissors,
这就意味着 是时候该...
which can only mean it's time...
修剪鼻毛啦
to trim some nose hairs!
卡尔真是疯狂
That Carl is crazy.
一年一度的婚纱特卖会...
The annual bridal sale...
-现在... -麦克斯 抓住我的手
- is now... - Max, hold my hand.
开始
Open!
女士们 女士们 一次只能拿一件
Ladies, ladies, one at a time.
虽然我可能得一瘸一拐地走红毯
Well, I may be limping down the aisle,
但好歹不用穿得像用来清洁吊扇灰尘的
but at least I won't be limping in something Swiffer might sell
黄毛掸子
to dust off ceiling fans.
天啊 妹子 她来了
Oh, my God, girl! Here she comes!
她来了
Here she comes.
是我的姐妹朗达 先抢到的这条裙子
My girl, Rhonda, had that dress first.
除非我死了
Oh, your girl is gonna have to
否则你得姐妹休想得到这条裙子
pry it out of my cold, dead hands.
麦克斯 卡洛琳
Hey, Max, Caroline!
快去试试
Try it on!
请跟着我到更衣室
Follow me to the changing room.
我不要穿着这条裙子出去 我怕怕
I'm never coming out in this dress, I'm scared.
那我数到三 一 二...
So on the count of one, two...
或许没那么难看呢
Maybe it's not that bad.
-难看死了 -难看死了
- It's bad. -- It's bad.
好吧 世界之大无奇不有
Okay. So you're telling me,
设计师范西哲被人谋杀
Versace got murdered,
却没人弄死设计这裙子的二逼吗
but no one's taken out whoever made these?
就是啊
I know.
感觉崔弟会因为侵权
I feel like Tweety Bird is gonna sue us
而把咱俩告上法庭
for copyright infringement.
感觉我们裙下藏着巨型的厕纸纸筒
I feel like we should have giant toilet paper rolls under here.
或许不在强光下
Well, maybe we'll like these better
我们会更喜欢这裙子
when we're out of this bright light.
麦克斯 我们就是闪瞎眼的强光
Max, we are the bright light.
女士们 你们忘记配套的帽子了
Ladies, you forgot the matching hats.
还有啊
There's more?
如果有人发现一颗"百忧解" 那是我的
Oh, if anyone finds a Xanax, it's mine.
有俩女人为了一条印花鱼尾裙大打出手
It was knocked out of my hand by two women duking it out
结果把药从我手里撞飞了
over a chintz mermaid dress.
现在我俩真是"漂亮"死了
Oh, now it looks good.
百忧解在外游荡 而我却在这傻站吗
There's Xanax on the loose and I'm just standing here?
至少我嗑药嗑嗨了 我还有个穿这玩意的借口
At least if I was high, I'd have an excuse to be wearing this.
出来吧 小药丸
Here pilly, pilly.
出来吧 小药丸子
Here pilly, pilly, pilly.
妹子 不是吧
Girl, for real,
你们穿这裙子真是难看屎了
you look like straight up crap in that dress.
真的
For real.
你们白人妞驾驭不了这个颜色
You white girls can't pull that color off.
真是浪费了这么跳的柠檬黄
That's a waste of poppin' lemon yellow.
我知道
I know.
我的确太白[人]了不适合
I am way too white for this.
她也"白"到不适合学黑人说"醉翻了"呢
She's also too white to say "turnt up" all the time,
但她还是会说啊
but that hasn't stopped her.
这裙子又不是我选的
This dress was not my choice.
我讨厌这裙子的一针一线
I hate everything about it.
这就是一场灾难
This is a disaster.
好一条"毁天灭地黄裙"
This is "dressageddon."
是 不过感觉还好啦
Yeah, but in a good way.
你们俩不想穿这条裙子
You two don't want to wear the dresses.
可以不用穿啊
You don't have to.
但我以为你想让我们呼应
But I thought you wanted us to match
气球和鸭子的颜色
the balloons and the ducks.
麦克斯 她说我们不用穿这裙子
Max, she said we don't have to wear the dress.
你就别质疑她了
Don't question her!
就像狱警说你可以走了
That's like questioning a prison guard
你还要质疑他的决定一样
when he says you're free to go.
苏菲 你确定你不介意吗
Sophie, are you sure you don't care?
是啊 当然不介意
Oh, yeah. Sure.
好啦 裙子归你们了 天命真女
Yeah, they're all yours, Destiny's Child.
这是重达9斤的鸡巴玩意
This is ten pounds of ugly junk.
让我想起我以前的约会对象 酒保皮特
Reminds me of this bartender, Pete, I used to date.
现在想想 那"玩意"也让我"作呕"
Come to think of it, that made me gag, too.
好了 结束了
Okay. Done.
你听 有人在试衣间里哭
listen, crying in a women's dressing room?
不管你是谁 妹子 现在流行大屁股
Whoever it is, girl, big butts are in.
那是苏菲的哭声
That's Sophie's cry.
我知道 我曾在通风孔听过她的哭声
I know, 'cause I hear it through the vent
当时她在看电视剧《音乐之乡》
when she watches Nashville.
苏菲
Sophie?
不是
No.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
不是我 但我没事
It's not me, but I'm okay.
苏菲 你为什么哭
Sophie, why are you crying?
当我听到你抱怨裙子的话时...
When I heard what you said about the dresses...
让我...
It's just--
感觉就像 有点像
It's almost, kind of like,
你觉得我的品味差之类的
you think I have bad taste or something.
没有
No.
卡洛琳觉得你的品味很棒
Caroline thinks you have great taste.
真的吗
She does?
那她说出来啊
Well, then she should say so.
现在就说
Now.
苏菲 我觉得你拥有独一无二的个人风格
Well, Sophie, I think you have your own unique style.
而我觉得...
And I think...
我没听见"很棒"或"品味"两个词
that I didn't hear the words "great" or "taste."
苏菲 你干嘛在乎我怎么想
Sophie, what do you even care what I think?
快说
Just say it!
苏菲 我觉得你的品味很棒
Sophie, I think you have great taste.
真的吗
You do?
那我们还在坐着干嘛
Then, what are we doing sitting here?
快去把那两条裙子抢回来
Let's go and get those dresses back!
快 帮我一下
Come on. Help me!
那俩妞已经把裙子买走了
Those other girls already took them.
什么
What?
至少我们不必穿着在婚礼上
Well, at least we don't have to wear those ugly,
穿着那条难看的黄色伴娘裙了
yellow bridesmaid dresses at the wedding.
是啊 现在你们只需在这穿着
Yup. Now, you only have to wear
这条难看的黄色制服裙 每晚都穿
ugly, yellow dresses here, every night.
这是发生在我身上最棒的事情了
This is the best thing that's happened to me
上次还是我发现我手臂上奇怪的痣
since I realized that weird mole on my arm was
只是一颗早餐麦片 不是癌症
just a Grape-Nut and not cancer.
姑娘们 好消息
Girls, great news.
你把阿憨塞进微波炉
You stuffed Han in the microwave
准备按下电源键吗
and you're ready to hit power?
拜托 我们早试过了
Come on. We've tried.
你知道他塞不进去
You know he doesn't fit.
唯一一样他太大进不去的东西
The one thing he's too big for.
我请伊利亚·乔比奇当我们的婚礼摄影师
No, I got Ilia Jorbich to be our wedding photographer.
他是《华沙时报》最厉害的摄影师
He's the best photographer at The Warsaw Times.
他也是唯一双臂还没被炸掉的摄影师
Well, he's the only one who still has both arms.
等等 所以是《华沙时报》
Wait, it's the Warsaw Times?
一直以来 我都以为是《纽约时报》
All this time, I've been thinking it was The New York Times.
《纽约时报》
New York Times?
这比它独家多了
This is much more exclusive.
你只能在两种地方买到
You can only get it in two places.
波兰和新泽西一家有卖导弹的熟食店
Poland and the deli in New Jersey that sells missiles.
这太棒了
This is amazing.
我在《纽约时报》的华丽回归的机会还在
My comeback in The New York Times has been preserved.
麦克斯 我要好好笑一个
Max, I'm gonna go ahead and smile.
我的生活又变美好了
My life is good again.
先别笑 苏菲告诉我
Don't smile yet, 'cause Sophie told me
因为你说她品味好
that because you said she had such good taste,
她要亲自设计我们的礼服
she's designing our dresses herself.
美梦一秒钟就破功了吗
What was that, like a second?
是啊 你刚直接从最美好的时光
Yup. You just went from the best of times
掉到了《华沙时光[报]》
to The Warsaw Times.